

N.ANAND
Shift Manager - B.SC

Dynamic career reflecting, record- breaking performance in F&B sales Management field with 7 years of experience which includes two preopening of stores. Educated in B.SC Hotel Management and Catering Technology Driven F&B with solid experience in customer service and staff supervision. Well-Rounded background with demonstrated strength in store Management, Team Management & shrinkage.

Core Competencies

- Adaptability
- Communication
- Flexibility
- Initiative
- Interpersonal Skills Leadership and Team Building

- CustomerService
- Staff Hiring&Development
- Business / Market
- **Awareness**
- Store

Chennai

+919566018524

anandinfo1994@gmail.com

- Operation
- Shrinkage/ Expenses
 - Control

Education

SRM University, Chennai.

B.SC in HOTEL MANAGEMENT

2011-2014

Professional Experience

Tablez Group Food Company, LULU GROUP DIVISION

Galitos Phoenix Mall, Chennai

> Shift- Manager From <u>December</u> 2021 - Present



2018 - 2019

Team Training
Manager From
May 2019 to
December 2020



Galitos White Field Restaurant Banglore

Training From
October 2018 to
Dec 2019



Dominos Pizza R.K Salai Mylapore

Training ACE &Platinum Team Member 2015 to 2018

- Responsible for overall success of the stores by directing all operational aspects to each stores and departments and driving sales whilst minimizing cost.
- Coach and develop department managers to achieve excellent standards, results and best practice.
- Ensure the delivery of operational KPIs and sales across stores and analyzing data which has an impact on store performance.
- Ensure uniformity & high standards of quality in terms of service managed at store, driving customer retention and strong loyalty.
- Led and motivated the store team to achieve the sale target and ensure efficiency
- Manage store output in terms of sell outs metrics, volumes, quantity per invoice.
- Followed cent percent SOP's at store
- Maintain optimum stock level for inventory & setting norms for timely inventory..Managed stock levels and taken key decisions in stock and wastage control.
- Analyzed the sales in figures and forecasted the future sales volume to maximize profits.
- Used the information technology to record the sales figures, data analysis and forward planning.
- Ensured all safety parameters are followed in all aspect of work units
- Monitoring sales team performance, analyzing sales data, periodical forecasting and reporting to Regional heads
- Managing brand marketing and promotions at partners.
- Managed Front Desk tasks for a 200-room full-service boutique hotel.
- Managed Front House Staff and conducted ongoing training.
- Executed opening/closing duties including; financial reports and verifying staff accuracy.

Notable Achievements

- Received Best Team Training Manager award for excellence in training for new joiners 2019.
- Promoted as Team Training manager to train the entire team of Forum mall & Phoenix Mall staff.
- Received Employee of the month honors and top scores on shopper reports with exceptionally high customer service remarks.
- Acted as face of company for social media sites and promoted the business outside of work.

PERSONAL PROFILE

T ETTOSTITEE						
Father's Name	Mr.P.Narayanan					
Mother's Name	Mrs.N.Sundari					
Sex	Male					
Nationality	Indian					
Date of Birth	18/02/1994					
	Name	Rea d	Spea k	Write		
Languages Known	Tamil	✓	√	√		
	English	√	√	√		
	Hindi					

REFERENCES

<u>Name</u>	<u>Designation</u>	Contact Number
Mr. Jinesh Chaco	Territory Manager –Galito's	+91 9034027786
Mr. Yatheesh	District Manager –Starbucks	+91 9738008477
Mr.Reji Joseph	Area Manager - Galito's	+91 7034009786
Mr. Ashok	Galito's Store Manager, Forum Mall	+91 9840017089

Date Signature